[
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "Which of these devices uses AI at home? / أي من هذه الأجهزة تستخدم الذكاء الاصطناعي في المنزل؟",
    "options": [
      "Gas oven / فرن الغاز",
      "Alexa or Siri",
      "Mirror / مرآة",
      "Flashlight / مصباح يدوي"
    ],
    "answer": "Alexa or Siri"
  },
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "Which can I share with Artificial Intelligence? / اي من الخيارات التاليه يمكنني مشاركتها مع الذكاء الاصطناعي؟",
    "options": [
      "Passwords / كلمات المرور",
      "Address / العنوان",
      "Family members names / اسماء افراد الاسره",
      "Scientific questions / أسئله علميه"
    ],
    "answer": "Scientific questions / أسئله علميه"
  },
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "Where does AI get its answers? / من أين يحصل الذكاء الاصطناعي على إجاباته؟",
    "options": [
      "From TV / من التلفاز",
      "Books / الكتب",
      "From stored data / من البيانات المخزنة",
      "Humans / الإنسان"
    ],
    "answer": "From stored data / من البيانات المخزنة"
  },
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What is a feature of AI? / ما هي ميزة الذكاء الاصطناعي؟",
    "options": [
      "Thinking and learning / التفكير والتعلم",
      "Cooking / الطبخ",
      "Handwriting / الكتابة اليدوية",
      "Flying planes / قيادة الطائرة"
    ],
    "answer": "Thinking and learning / التفكير والتعلم"
  },
  {
    "type": "TF",
    "question": "Is AI always correct? / هل الذكاء الاصطناعي دائمًا على حق؟",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What is Artificial Intelligence? / ما هو الذكاء الاصطناعي؟",
    "options": [
      "Human robot / انسان الي",
      "Application learns and takes decisions / برنامج يتعلم ويتخاذ القرارات",
      "New language / لغه جديده",
      "A game / لعبه"
    ],
    "answer": "Application learns and takes decisions / برنامج يتعلم ويتخاذ القرارات"
  },
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "How does Artificial Intelligence learn? / كيف يتعلم الذكاء الاصطناعي؟",
    "options": [
      "Playing games / بلعب الألعاب",
      "Watching movies / بمشاهدة الأفلام",
      "Listening to music / بالاستماع إلى الموسيقى",
      "Studying data / بدراسة البيانات"
    ],
    "answer": "Studying data / بدراسة البيانات"
  },
  {
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "Can you share your personal photo with Artificial Intelligence? / هل يمكنك مشاركة صورتك الشخصية مع الذكاء الصناعي؟",
    "options": [
      "Yes / نعم",
      "No / لا",
      "Yes if I was at home / نعم، إذا كنت في المنزل",
      "Yes if someone told me to do so / فقط إذا طلب مني أحد ذلك"
    ],
    "answer": "No / لا"
  },
    {
    "type": "TF",
    "question": "AI can help us with homework and research / يمكن للذكاء الاصطناعي مساعدتنا في فهم الدروس",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "type": "TF",
    "question": "AI needs data to improve its performance / يحتاج الذكاء الاصطناعي إلى البيانات لتحسين أدائه",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "type": "TF",
    "question": "It is safe to share personal information with AI / من الآمن مشاركة معلومات سكني مع الذكاء الاصطناعي",
    "answer": "false"
  }
]